## THOMAS MOSKAL

Auburn, NY. 13021 MoskalTM@gmail.com • 315-877-6614

Experienced team coordinator, excelling in diverse, fast-paced environments. Exceptional experience in interpersonal communication while possessing an avid interest in current developments in the fields of Computer Science, IoT, virtual/augmented reality for disabled people and service management. Dedicated, ethical and motivated. Committed to outstanding customer service while maintaining confidence and poise in interactions with all individuals.

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Communication

Adaptation

Teamwork

Organization

Critical Analysis

• Multi-tasking

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Belvista Software** – Rochester, New York

Intern / Database associate -(11/2022 - 5/2023)

Queried multiple databases in MySQL to analyze information relevant to our clients. Constructed SSRS reports made to the specifications of clients using these queries. Had to learn terms specific to the financial industry. Gained experience with remote work environments and how to communicate effectively with others remotely. Leadership had a focus on paying attention to what the client really needs.

Skaneateles Country Club – Skaneateles, New York Banquet Chef – (4/2018-12/2019, 6/2022 – 9/2022)

Primarily fulfilled banquet chef position. This included organizing time, people, and product at the same time in a fast-paced environment to feed hundreds of people at a time. Handled ordering of food and scheduling. Filled any necessary position if I was free; for example, working on the line for lunch and dinner shifts, expediting. During a 2-week period there was no Executive Chef, I took over the responsibility of that role until the replacement was able to join the team. Worked long periods of time, upwards of 12 hours for multiple days in a row during the busy season.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

SUNY Oswego, Oswego, New York (8/2021 – 8/2023) - Computer Science B.S. Onondaga Community College, Syracuse, New York (08/2020-5/2021) – Computer Science A.S.

Paul Smith's College, Paul Smiths, New York (08/2015-12/2017) – Culinary Arts and Service Management Onondaga Community College, Syracuse, New York (05/2011, 08/2013) – Hospitality/Restaurant Management Liverpool High School, Liverpool, New York (05/2009) – High school Diploma

Proficient in Java, HTML, C, Racket, Arduino, Microsoft word, PowerPoint, Excel

Recently completed several projects including: Common Lisp CLOS; Wikipedia recommendations based on K-medoids and Hash arrays; A web service which uses a Pi microcontroller to monitor conditions and water a user's houseplant remotely.

School website: https://habshanty.github.io/

GitHub page: https://github.com/HabShanty?tab=repositories

3.51 GPA at SUNY Oswego